

PROFILE

I belong to rajasthan in Udaipur distick. I live in Ahmedabad in vejalpur. I have completed my m.com and b.com from gujarat university. I have 3.5 year experience in account field. I work on account executive at JPA trading firm. I serve notice period.

CONTACT

PHONE: 9998118783 EMAIL:

Shyamgirigoswami29@gmail.com

PERSONAL DETAILS

Father's name – Dev Giri Goswami

Mother's name – Meena Devi

Gender - Male Status - Married Nationality - Indian Age - 26 Year

Language Known – Eng & Hindi &

Gujrati

HOBBIES

Reading religious books learn Music

SHYAM GIRI GOSWAMI

Accounts Executive

EDUCATION

M.COM (External)

Dec 2016 - Apr 2018

I have completed my Master of Commerce (M.Com) from at Gujarat University Ahmedabad in 2018.

B.COM (Regular)

Dec 2012 - Apr 2015

I have completed my Bachelor of Commerce (B.Com) from H.A.C.C college at Gujarat university Ahmedabad in 2015.

WORK EXPERIENCE

JPA TRADING LLP (Account Executives)

14 Aug 2020 -31 Dec 2020

I am Accounts Executive at JPA Trading LLP firm. JPA Trading is trading firm to sales yarn out of gujarat and monthly turn-over more than 32 crores. Looking forward responsibility:-

- Make purchase order and follow-up.
- Book Keeping and pass necessary journal entry purchase, sales, Receipt, payment j/v in tally Erp software.
- Make payment all creditor, commission agent, salary and wages.
- Handle all office administrative expenses.
- GST (GSTR1, GSTR2B, GSTR3B)
- TDS (Comp. & Non-Comp.)
- TCS (Comp. & Non-Comp.)
- MIS (Sales Report)
- Bank reconciliation

IRM LTD (Account officer)

08 Jul 2019 –31 Jul 2020

I am Accounts officer at IRM Ltd. IRM Ltd is substitute company of Cadila pharmaceutical Itd. And monthly turn-over 1 crore. IRM Itd provide three services of canteen, guest house, rent-cab, bakkary services to cadila employee of different location bhat gujarat, delhi, Mumbai, banglore and jammu kashmier. Bakery service provider in counter sale of bhat, Apollo hospital, dholka, kos.

- Invoice/Kot/ Challan invoked from all locations Mum, Delhi, Jammu, banalore Bhat.
- Make sales invoice base on all received challan/Kot from different Location.
- Cash collection from counter sale Apollo, Bhat, Kos and deposited to bank
- Book keeping and make cheque for vender payment.
- Every month make billing summary mail all respective department.
- All bill submission in bhat corporate office respective department.
- Bank reconciliation and short out query of auditor.

Future Retail Ltd. (Commercial Co-ordinator)

19 May 2017 - 03 Jun 2019

I join future retail Itd as a fresher and it's first job in my career. I work on commercial department as a co-ordinate. Furure retail Itd is retail company to sale all garments food item many think day to day use item in life at one platform like big bazzar mall etc. it is big company and have many branches open diff diff location. I work on two software sap and omani. Omni software is ganaret invoice recording and sap software is make booking. Looking forward responsibility:-

- Purchase invoice booking as per p.o.
- Checking invoice as per GST compliance.
- Creating query and resolving regarding goods inword.
- Non salable goods invoice indexing processing and booking.
- Use T code: zmiro1, miro, fbo3, fb60.

SKILLS

- Tally erp 9
- Ms- office, Ms Word, Advance excel.
- Communication skills
- Ability to accept challenges.